Guide to the John and Ann Garvey Papers AIA.088
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Irish American Organizations, 1935-2019; 10.15 linear feet in 18 manuscript boxes, 3 folders in an oversize box, and 2 folders in 2 shared oversize boxes
  - Gaelic Athletic Association of Greater New York: Annual Banquet Programs, 2011, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Gaelic League, undated (Box 22, Folder 5-6)
  - Galway Association of New York - 119th Annual St. Patrick Dinner Dance, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Glor Achadh Mor, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Ireland Chamber of Commerce (US): Celtic Ball Program, 2014-2015 (Box 14, Folder 4, Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Irish American Archives Association, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 15, Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Irish American Parade Committee, Inc. (Brooklyn): 39th Annual Installation Dance Booklet, 2014 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Irish American Society of Nassau, Suffolk, and Queens, 1991, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 5, Box 22, Folder 4, Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Irish American Writers and Artists: Eugene O'Neill Lifetime Achievement Award, 2010, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Irish Ancestral Research Association (Sudbury, MA), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Irish Apostolate Dinner Dance Program, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Irish Cultural Centre, 2012, 2014-2015 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Irish Cultural Society, 2020 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Irish Cultural Society (Garden City, NJ), 2004-2019 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Irish Family History Forum: Newsletters, circa 2012-2019 (Box 14, Folder 9, Box 22, Folder 1, Folder 4)
  - Irish Family History Foundation, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Irish Genealogical Society: Newsletter (The Septs), 1991-1998 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - The Irish Repertory Theatre, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Leitrim Society NY Event Book, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - New Haven Gaelic Football and Hurling Club, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Newsletters and Ephemera from Multiple Organizations, 2000-2019 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ohio Irish American News, 2018 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - O'Shea, Gerry - UICA 1916 Commemoration Committee, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Our Lady of Knock Shrine Dedication Journal, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Requiem Mass for John Curry Program, 2017 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades: General, 1997-2020 (Box 15, Folder 1, Box 18, Box 22, Folder 3)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades: Brooklyn, 2011-2013 (Box 15, Folder 2-4)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades: New York City, 1995-2020 (Box 15, Folder 5-9, Box 16, Folder 1-2, Box 31, Folder 5-6, Box 32, Box 33, Folder 6, Folder 8)
  - St. Patrick's Day Parades: Photographs, 1991, undated (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Tara Circle, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - The Tara Circle: The Harvest Ball Program, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Centennial Committee, 2015 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Centennial Committee - Expenses, 2016 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Centennial Committee - Research, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Commemoration Committee, 2015-2016 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Commemoration Committee - Agendas, 2015 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Commemoration Committee - John Ridge, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Commemorative Materials, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: 1916 Easter Rising Committee, 2014-2016 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Annual Banquet Programs, 1997, 2012-2015 (Box 16, Folder 7, Box 30, Folder 4, Folder 6, Box 31, Folder 3, Box 34)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Centennial Dinner Dance Program, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Constitution Revision, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Dance, 2014 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Drafts, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Ephemera, Correspondence, 2015-2016 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Essays and Drafts, 2016 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Feis Progams, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: General, 1991-2018 (Box 16, Folder 4, Box 25, Folder 1, Box 30, Folder 8)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York: Meeting Notes, Financial Report, 2015-2016 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - United Irish Counties Association (UICA) of New York (likely): Contact Sheet, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - United Irish Counties Events (Photographs), undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - United Irish Counties and Irish Consulate: 1916 Centennial Committee - Minutes, 2014-2016 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Yeats Society of New York, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - The West Side Irish-American Club Historical Souvenir Booklet, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)